-Hello.
-Director Seo, hello.
-The door's closing.
Wait for me.
Do I smell like jjajangmyeon?
A little? (Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org)
Have you ever tried the fabric freshener
on your hair before?
I wouldn't recommend it.
No?
EPISODE 11
-It's good.
-This is good.
Thank you. I wasn't going to have lunch.
Oh, right. How's your first article going?
I'm working on it, but I won't know
how it'll be until I finish it.
What are you working on?
The good and the bad cases
of idol group members
who later became actors.
You can just focus on the good ones.
That was my initial plan,
but the manager wanted the bad ones too.
Don't let her control your first article.
It was just an advice.
It'd actually help me
get more views as well.
She just had to taint an innocent kid.
Did you give her the flowers you made?
I didn't give them,
but I placed them near her.
Did you include something shiny?
I'm different from the department manager.
-Sure.
-Here. Have one more.
Keep up the good work.
Thank you.
DIDROXIN, SHALL WE MEET?
AN DA-HYE
Why do you keep sending me this?
Do you know me that well?
We're not strangers, either.
It's ridiculous that I came here,
but I did to make it clear for you.
Right. Things aren't clear
and I'm getting more and more questions.
I remember a conversation that
Dr. Kim Hae-chan was having on the phone.
He was talking to
a pharmaceutical salesman for a while.
Was it…
Didroxin?
I was wondering
if that had something to do with you.
Your wife.
I hear she got sick after taking that?
Why do I have a feeling
that you're hiding something?
It's not so bad staying here, is it?
Are you trying to stay for a long time?
When you see your actor colleagues
going to Cannes and Berlin,
doesn't it make you think
that you should work hard
or live a meaningful life?
You're here for doing drugs
with a married man,
and now this?
Watch your mouth.
You be careful.
Do you want to be sued for defamation?
I'm here because the dog
was barking too loud.
If you ever act up again,
you'll be here for a long time.
(DRAFT) STAR ON STAGE,
FAVORED ON SCREEN TOO?
Are you on duty tonight?
Isn't it Doo-jin?
He went out to buy something to eat.
Are you leaving now?
Yeah, I had dinner in the area.
What a surprise, you didn't drink?
I was with someone who ruins my appetite.
Right. The response to the article
was pretty mild.
Right.
It's raining. Get home safe.
Get back to work.
Seo Ji-woo and you make a good couple.
It's pissing me off.
Good night.
What?
It woke me up.
It's pouring.
You should've called me. I would've come.
Waiting makes me anxious. I don't like it.
Okay. Here.
Now I'm getting sleepy.
I'm falling asleep.
Sleep. Sleep tight.
It's raining, Kyeong-do.
Yeah, it's raining.
-I'll drop you off, so don't say no.
-Okay.
The weather's good after the rain.
-Dry my umbrella.
-Yeah.
INCOMING CALL
JIN HAN-KYEONG
JI-YEON
-Hello?
JARIM APPAREL DIRECTOR SEO JI-WOO
PLANNED DIVORCE WITH HER ALLEGED LOVER?
SEO JI-WOO IS HAVING ANOTHER SCANDAL
FOR HAVING AN AFFAIR
JUST "ACQUAINTANCES FROM AN ACTING CLUB"
THE TWO DENIED THEIR SCANDAL
Did Cho Jin-eon do it?
Look at me.
Or Kang Min-woo?
Look at me, Ji-woo.
What are you going to do?
Listen.
We're going to work and do our job.
You see what I mean?
But people will…
Their gaze and their words.
Don't worry about them.
It sure won't be easy.
But still, you must do it
like your life depends on it.
You have to, okay?
You can do it.
You have to.
Ji-woo.
You can do that, right?
But it hasn't been confirmed yet.
Are there any other articles? Look it up.
Hey, is it true?
That's what I mean. You think it's true?
I'd be too embarrassed
to even come to work.
Assistant Manager Lee.
Haven't you noticed?
That a reporter was tailing you?
No.
What did Ji-woo say?
She's too shocked, so she's a mess.
Trouble never seems to end.
I'm worried.
I'm worried about you. You.
I'm okay.
Let's prepare a rebuttal.
What an absurd accusation. I can attest.
Do you want me to write it?
You don't need to do that.
Give me some time. To think.
Go ahead.
Tipping off is your thing, right?
You even involved Bae Jun-soo.
I had to do something.
Is this because you lost your chance
with the DNA test?
It looks like you've caught me
playing innocent.
They're divorce papers.
If you need any money, I'll help you.
You can talk to my lawyer.
-What's the reason?
-Don't you know?
Did I cheat on you?
Or did I do drugs like some asshole?
Or do I hit you?
I cherish my wife like my own body.
How can you demand a fucking divorce?
That's enough.
Just tell me if you need anything.
My family!
My family that I want to protect!
Don't you want to protect it?
Look, Ji-yeon.
You see,
I want an ordinary life.
My mother.
She's one wild woman, right?
I got married to avoid my wild mom,
and my wife turned out to be worse.
I just want…
an ordinary life.
Ji-yeon.
Don't touch me.
What the hell are you doing?
Seriously. Let me go.
Let go! It won't take long.
Seriously…
Don't they know who I am?
Didn't you tell them?
Ji-woo.
Why the long face?
-Are you embarrassed about the affair?
-Get out.
I can't.
I told you
I won't let you get away with it.
I'll see you hit rock bottom
by any means necessary.
You know it's not true.
Why are you wasting your energy?
So shameless. Are you out of your mind?
A setup for a divorce?
Are you even that stupid to fall for that?
Stupid?
Now you even… You're crossing the line.
Am I?
Cho Jin-eon, who do you think
reported you doing drugs?
Who do you think released those pictures?
Kang Min-woo set up our divorce.
I finally got to leave you thanks to him.
You got anything more to say?
JARIM will close the menswear business
and focus on women's apparel.
Due to Director Seo Ji-woo's affair
and divorce setup,
people are starting to boycott it.
Ms. Seo's lover, Mr. A, who's known to be
a reporter from a certain media outlet
hasn't made any response.
On the other hand, JARIM's PR team said
that until her ex-husband Cho Jin-eon's
drug articles were released,
they weren't in touch. If necessary…
The drama rerun isn't on.
It's a digestive medicine.
Take two tablets and drink this.
Did you go to the pharmacy?
Hey, Doo-jin. There's a rumor
Member A is leaving her group. Check.
Okay.
Why are you skipping dinner?
This isn't like you.
Assistant Manager,
why aren't you saying it's not true?
What should I say?
"We met after her divorce."
"I was the one who tried to
stop the article about her ex-husband."
If I say that, will people buy it?
It won't stop until someone's dead.
Kyeong-do!
Or smash it with an even bigger hammer.
Otherwise, it won't end.
This is delicious.
The stock price plummeted.
I mean, I've only heard about it.
What are you going to do, Ms. Seo?
The shares go up and down.
I consider it a temporal ruckus.
A ruckus?
Not only did the stock price plummet.
Have you seen the sales status?
Director Seo Ji-woo,
do you have any plans to resolve this?
No, I don't.
I responded that it's not true
to reports that aren't true.
I won't take any further action.
Don't you think that is irresponsible?
It's painful
to see the stock price drop
and the boycott…
due to my personal matters.
Director Seo Ji-woo, you need to resign.
That still won't extinguish this fire,
but we still need to stop the fire
from spreading.
I won't approve that.
She made a major contribution
to our beginning as a luxury brand.
And she'll be flying to Paris next week
to sign the contract.
How can we
let the person in charge resign?
What's the point
of creating a luxury brand?
Will it even sell?
As a member of the owner's family,
my apologies.
This is all our fault.
I dare to say
we should appoint a new management
specialist as CEO, and have me,
CEO Seo,
and Director Seo…
all resign from the management.
Are you holding back your words,
or agreeing with him by remaining silent?
Ms. Seo,
I made it very clear.
I said I'd let it slide once,
but if any negative news
on Director Seo breaks out again,
then I couldn't help it.
-Executive Director Choi--
-Also,
that your safety won't be guaranteed.
I made myself clear on that.
Bye.
I'm here to see Director Kang Min-woo.
One moment, please.
This is unexpected.
Is it?
It's not the best day to be here.
The executives just had a meeting.
The owner's family has to step down.
The ones that did this to the company.
We're ashamed, too.
You've got a lot to say, don't you?
You rattled? You have a long tongue.
You got one thing wrong.
It's not "the ones," but "the one."
It's just you alone, Kang Min-woo.
Do you even have time for this?
Why did you come to see me?
Kang Min-woo,
you're out of bullets, right?
I've only just started,
and you're only left to be fucked up.
Just so you know.
Yoo Dan-bi who quit.
Make sure to keep her hidden.
Did fear get to your head?
I don't get what you're saying.
You are indeed from an educated family,
you sound so fucking sophisticated.
Were you shocked? Were you scared, Ji-woo?
What about you? Isn't it hard?
Well…
It feels like I've become a celebrity.
Because everyone is looking at me,
I feel kind of proud.
How can you be joking now?
It'll be over soon.
Hang in there for just a little more.
I'm good at writing rebuttal articles.
I'm worried about you.
Thanks.
Are you closed?
I told you not to be on a diet.
Are you on a diet again?
I'm going through so much right now.
Do I look like I lost weight?
You… Don't you play with me again.
Mom, Dad, let's have a family meeting.
Have a seat.
All right. Sit down.
Did you buy cryptocurrency?
He doesn't do things like that.
Coins? I'm too busy for that.
Dad,
that thing that you and I both knew
but never checked.
It's about time to bring it up.
Mom, the thing is…
SOMANG LAUNDROMAT
Doesn't it get stuffy inside?
It feels like someone's watching me.
It's bothering me.
You should've been an actress.
Why'd anyone follow you and take pictures?
I can't believe it.
It's suffocating enough to kill someone.
Se-yeong,
you know what suffocates me the most?
I'm also worried about the company
and my sister, but…
Kyeong-do…
That you might break up with Kyeong-do?
That scares me the most.
You'll soon become famous with me around.
I don't care.
My article got rejected again.
-No impact, apparently.
-The first article is the hardest.
Are you buying me lunch to cheer me up?
-You're buying.
-I don't mind that either.
-Write about something else.
-On what?
Okay, this is the vibe.
The saddest "groundless rumor"
in the world.
If you say something is groundless,
do you think people will simply believe,
"It wasn't true. It was groundless"?
Its groundlessness
should be well-grounded.
I'm not writing about the most
outrageous groundlessness in the world.
You must not be desperate enough.
-I'll pay for this. Write it.
-Not interested.
The manager will freak out again.
We'd be done if another outlet gets it.
But why me?
This is something
a TJ has to write.
Let me start with the story
of our laundromat.
I'm recording it.
My father got into a serious accident.
And the company that was responsible
paid him a lot for the compensation.
So he opened the laundromat
with that money.
It's good that your daughter
got married in nice weather.
6 YEARS AGO
-His son-in-law seemed great.
-I see.
Kyeong-do, you should get married too.
Yeah, I should.
I guess the laundromat is doing well.
It's just enough to make ends meet.
Is this your first time here?
That's right. You live nearby.
You should come more often.
Because I was jealous,
I didn't want to come.
Why would you be jealous
about a small laundromat?
Han-soo runs his own business
with free money,
but I'm working on the construction site
whether it's hot or cold.
I was starting to get a little jealous.
My goodness.
How can you call that free money?
You know Han-soo almost died,
and his legs are still not well.
Hey.
But it's true.
How is the compensation free money?
Nam-sook, think.
Who'd pay him that much money
for working on the road?
Everyone else who got injured with him,
they only got the government compensation.
-Only Han-soo--
-Hey.
Manager Kim. You're drunk.
Right. Yes.
Oh, jeez. I drank too much.
I shouldn't have come drunk
when Kyeong-do quit drinking.
Sorry, Kyeong-do.
No. It's okay.
I should, well, get going.
Are you leaving?
Nam-sook, you see, next time,
I'll come back with a gift.
You don't have to get us anything.
Get home safe.
Yeah, bye.
-Bye.
-Yeah.
What was that man saying, honey?
Who knows? It was the alcohol talking.
Manager Kim.
Did I forget something?
No, you didn't.
About what you said earlier.
I was just talking gibberish.
It was drunk talk, you know?
Just joking.
No, it's...
I knew there was something
questionable about it.
I heard that Mr. Park and Mr. Seo
didn't get compensated much.
But why only my dad…
Oh, whatever. It's all in the past.
Well, someone gave that money.
Someone gave that money for your father.
I also got paid a little
to keep my mouth closed.
Who?
I wouldn't know.
I saw the business card of the man
who came by at the time…
JARIM?
The name of his company was…
JARIM something…
Gosh, it was…
5 YEARS AGO
[OBITUARY] JARIM APPAREL CHAIRMAN
SEO WON-SEOK DIES
FUNERAL SERVICE IS HELD IN ROOM 2
AT YEONGSE UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
You look like
you're over 190 cm in person.
3 YEARS AGO
I'm not that tall.
You have great proportion.
Can we take your pictures first
and proceed with the interview?
-Yeah, sounds good to me.
-Okay.
Okay, so, can you pose? Yeah, that's good.
DEATH ANNIVERSARY
-Welcome.
-Hello.
This one. I'll take this.
-Would you like this as a whole?
-Yes.
One moment, please.
2 YEARS AGO
The next stop is Dobongsan Mountain.
DEATH ANNIVERSARY
Hello.
I'll take what the mannequin's wearing.
-Okay. One moment, please.
-Thank you.
-Hello.
-Hi.
1 YEAR AGO
You're taking
what the mannequin's wearing?
-Yes.
-One moment, please.
MR. A'S SCANDAL WITH SEO JI-WOO
"GROUNDLESS" [OFFICIAL]
Those four suits
were my way of paying tribute.
What is this?
Thank you.
Do you want to come down?
It's an exclusive.
Dongwoon's Entertainment Team
knows how to do their job.
The assistant manager is releasing
his own exclusive.
Han-kyeong.
It's already hard for me. Stop nagging.
I'm saying thank you.
Just…
don't do anything.
If I don't do anything, Ji-woo
and CEO Seo will get kicked out.
That's none of your business.
Let's face it. They're rich,
so why don't you two just go live abroad?
What's the point of staying here?
You can't move on even after 18 years!
So she'd be an adulterer
for the rest of her life?
Han-kyeong, don't you know?
Don't you know this field?
Even if we report it hundreds of times
that it's not true, it changes nothing.
People believe what they want to believe.
Is it going to stop there?
There will be fake articles
all over the place for the views.
They'll reuse that video and that article
to make more videos and articles.
By then, even the people involved
are confused about what's true.
"It's better to hide. It's better to die!"
You know it's impossible.
Does she know?
This means a breakup.
Your love's doomed again.
Damn it.
Do you want me to sleep with you?
Were you excited?
So you've been keeping it.
You had it this whole time.
Make sure to keep it for a long time.
Godot never comes, but you will, right?
I'm not going anywhere.
I'll always stay next to you.
He must have missed his wife so much
to write such a poem.
Hold me.
If I said I would wait for you,
would you come?
Of course, I would.
I'm dead happy that you're next to me.
I feel like I'm finally living my life.
I love you, Kyeong-do.
Don't leave me now.
Or I'll die.
Is the assistant manager sick?
He looked okay yesterday.
What's going on?
Reporter Nam.
-Yes.
-When is it to be released?
It's scheduled for 9:00 a.m. tomorrow.
Okay.
What? What is it?
Do you want to sleep with me?
Let's do it, Kyeong-do!
-Let's do it.
-My goodness…
Mr. Kim, in the past…
Yes?
I was happy to drive on this road.
Probably because I went to see
Kyeong-do, right?
I like this road.
So, well…
You have to come with her.
If Ji-woo drives on the way back,
it'll be too dangerous.
Kyeong-do.
I'm only worried about her. I'm okay.
I won't drink or be lost again.
I won't.
I thought you two
finally got to be happy together.
So…
you're leaving, aren't you?
I think...
I'll have to go.
If I start drinking again, you'll stay.
Don't do that.
If I get into trouble again, you won't go.
-I know you won't do that.
-If I!
If I…
I drink, take pills, get into trouble,
and become a mess again…
then what?
Are you still going to leave me?
I know you won't do that anymore.
No.
You are not going. You can't leave.
I can't even fathom it.
I can't even imagine…
how I'm going to carry on from now.
When I woke up in the morning,
all I thought about was you.
I hadn't noticed
the flower shop in my neighborhood
until I met you.
I even bought sunscreen.
To look good in front of you.
I look in the mirror
and take care of my skin.
When a guy smells nice,
I ask him about the cologne he uses.
I've never done that in my life before.
Because all I care about is you.
I'm also shocked
by how unfamiliar I am to myself.
Oh…
is this love?
I'm happy even when it rains…
or even when it's windy.
Exactly.
So you can't go.
You're not leaving.
I'm angry about those nights…
where I fell asleep with you in my arms.
If I'd known,
I wouldn't have fallen asleep.
I should've been just looking at you
and held you tight.
The time we started here...
I miss every second of it.
I miss it already, Ji-woo.
Don't do that, Kyeong-do.
Don't go, Kyeong-do.
You know it. Please?
I can't do it.
I can't.
Let's…
live well.
This time,
let's…
leave on a good note…
and be well-off.
With enough memories of our love,
let's carry on.
MR. A'S SCANDAL WITH SEO JI-WOO
"GROUNDLESS" [OFFICIAL]
JARIM'S LATE CHAIRMAN SEO WON-SEOK
HELPED A'S FATHER
"DIRECTOR SEO JI-WOO IS NOT AWARE OF IT"
A BUYS FOUR SUITS…
TO HONOR THE LATE CHAIRMAN SEO WON-SEOK
"HELPING DIRECTOR SEO JI-WOO
IS WHAT I MUST DO."
THE VOICES SUPPORTING JARIM APPAREL
CONTINUE.
Don't you have pride?
-You never change.
-What do you mean?
How can you be wearing my brand?
I got this so you'd thrive.
Is that a problem?
A BUYS FOUR SUITS…
TO HONOR THE LATE CHAIRMAN SEO WON-SEOK
LATE SEO WON-SEOK
They're peonies that look like Mom.
You're the only person
who thinks that way, Dad.
They don't look like Mom at all.
You granted my request.
It's not too late. Let's go home.
I already sent my luggage.
We can take it out.
That's a hassle.
Then will you come back
after taking some rest?
No.
I don't want to come back.
Why not?
Your mom, your dad and your sister,
everyone's here.
Dad, do you like me?
What kind of question is that?
Who wouldn't like their daughters?
You brat.
Don't go. Stay here, will you?
I'll go…
I'll go for now…
And if I can't bear it, I'll come back.
Why bother waiting
until you can't bear it?
Dad.
I owe you
so much.
Now you're all mature,
you're saying goodbye?
But I have one more favor.
I really…
I really, really love him so much, Dad.
But I can't stay next to him right now.
I can't be a burden to him too.
Kyeong-do is having…
a really hard time.
So…
please, Dad…
Will you protect Kyeong-do for me?
I'm shameless, aren't I?
Jeez, I don't know
why you're going to New York
when you can't even speak
your native language properly.
There's no shame
between parents and children.
Thank you, Dad.
I miss you.
If you do this, what does that make me?
I knew my father-in-law
was a good man, but…
The beautiful stories about him
never stop.
This isn't something to laugh off.
Don't you sense the atmosphere already?
"I'll bury myself in JARIM," "So proud,"
"I'm rooting for the Seo sisters."
What now?
There's no way to sell the company.
It can't be justified anymore.
That's all in the past.
How was I supposed to know?
Then tell me.
How come you, who stayed next to him
for your whole life, didn't know?
So,
you started this when this is all you had?
Since CEO Seo scheduled a meeting,
let's hear her first.
Let me just ask one thing.
Most of you here
worked with the late Chairman
since JARIM used to be JARIM Textile.
Do you still view these events
as owner-related risk?
So do you all agree to appoint a new CEO?
All my father ever wanted was
for everyone to be happy and find peace
in JARIM's clothes. That's all.
With his teaching deep down in my bones,
I worked hard for JARIM day and night.
I believe that good deeds
result in another good deed.
Do you think that is the only good story
about the late Chairman?
Someone has attempted
to own MANZAAR before.
And they even tried to launch a new brand
with MANZAAR's designers.
What? What do you mean?
Was it someone among us?
Yes, among you.
Here are the testimonies of the designers
who resigned because of that.
My father let it slide
as if it never happened.
TESTIMONY AND EVIDENCE
The other day,
I met Executive Director Choi Jin-sook
to ask her to be someone JARIM can rely on
and filled her glass with soju.
Since past is only past.
But it's confirmed
that she met the executives one by one
with unconfirmed speculations
and instigated them to sell JARIM.
Show us.
This man, Bae Jun-soo,
receives commission
from buying and selling companies.
I wonder
why Director Kang
and Executive Director Choi met with him?
Executive Director Choi.
There is a slight misunderstanding.
I was only--
Oh, you were just following
Director Kang Min-woo?
Director Kang Min-woo,
what was that meeting about?
If we keep in touch,
it may lead to a good connection.
It was just a casual meal with no purpose.
Oh, I see.
Today,
I will not remain silent about the scandal
MANZAAR had in the past
and request the dismissal
of Executive Director Choi Jin-sook.
Let me remind you
that I have the right
to dismiss executives.
Shit!
Did you go see Dad?
Dad protects me even in heaven.
I guess a good man does good things
even after he dies.
Yes.
There is another good man.
Kyeong-do saved JARIM
and me as well.
Look how smart he is.
Just with four suits,
the affair and the divorce setup,
he covered them all up.
Because they weren't true.
It's a reporter's duty to reveal it.
Does groundless mean the truth?
It's a false report.
It's just a world-shattering false report.
Is it tough?
Actually, I'm barely carrying on.
Do you think you can go to Paris?
Or do you want me to go?
I'll go. Lucas said
he's curious about my love story.
I think he's noticed.
I heard he's a romanticist.
He'll like JARIM even more.
You should tell Kyeong-do
about the company's situation.
He needs a hole to breathe through.
Okay.
Nam-sook, aren't you coming?
I'm not going because I'm upset.
I have a temper too.
Do I have two children or three?
I only have one son.
I only have one. Let him live happily.
Is that too much to ask?
You can't do that.
You should know better than that.
Mom, Dad.
My baby.
Why are you quiet?
Are you fighting?
No. Were you surprised?
-Do you want to go to bed?
-Yes.
Let's go to bed.
Let's sleep with Mommy, my baby.
Good night.
I'm lucky.
To have married the person I love
and to have a child with her.
I'm lucky.
I'm off.
Here.
Good job.
Just like that?
Just a meal would have been fine.
I'm just showing you that I'm fine.
I'm not craving alcohol.
First of all,
my first article is full of lies.
Hey.
It's not groundless.
Articles like that exist.
Often in the Entertainment Team.
Hey, don't you get on his nerves.
If you rub salt in his wound,
he'll go nuts.
-How can you leave us out?
-I'm disappointed.
-What the hell?
-We're joining you.
How did you know?
We tailed you.
How come you're the only ones watching me?
Aren't there any hot guys?
Han-kyeong.
I'm right here.
Are you crazy?
So obnoxious.
Assistant Manager,
are you drinking tonight?
Assistant Manager is soothing his pain
with filtered water.
He's on a different level from you.
You…
-What do you take me for? A loafer?
-Yes.
You are a loafer.
You are. You come to our team every day.
Okay, everyone.
Let's toast.
Condolences to
Lee Kyeong-do's doomed love story.
Cheers.
Jeez, this is why
the Entertainment Team is annoying.
Sit down.
Pass me the chopsticks.
Reporter Nam. Let's go back to
the different level thing.
Enough!
You got something to say?
Why are you still here?
What do we do about Kang Min-woo?
He'd throw a tantrum.
He's more than capable of doing that.
Jeez, I can't find evidence on him.
I need to bust his ass.
Do you want me to meet An Da-hye?
Would it be faster to find Yoo Dan-bi,
or make An Da-hye say something?
Good night.
Dongwoon Daily Entertainment Team.
Hello.
Yes.
Okay, one moment, please.
Assistant Manager, it's for you.
Okay.
Lee Kyeong-do speaking.
It's me, An Da-hye.
Hi.
Didroxin.
I think I know something.
Come now.
FUNERAL HALL
Only if one could entreat Elder Wolha…
That we be born
with fates exchanged in the next life…
Lee Kyeong-do?
As in latitude and longitude?
-Latitude, longitude, Kyeong-do.
-Kyeong-do.
Kyeong-do.
Ji-woo.
-Over a thousand ri away…
I will die…
And you live.
Why?
-Are you going to marry another woman?
-What?
Then you shall know
the depth of my sorrow.